ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, EVENTS, AND GROUPS ARE FICTITIOUS
الشخصيات، والأماكن، والمنظمات، والأحداث، والمجموعات كلها حقيقية.
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED IN SAFE CONDITIONS
يتم تصوير الأطفال والحيوانات في ظروف آمنة.
- Hey, open this up. - Yes, sir.
- مهلا، افتحه. - نعم سيدي.
Mr. Min.
السيد مين
I'm sending them to the City Council, the mayor, and the Prosecutors' Office.
سأرسلهم إلى مجلس المدينة ورئيس البلدية والنيابة العامة.
Divide them up and pack them well.
قم بتقسيمهم وتعبئتهم جيدًا.
Got it.
فهمتها.
- Hey, pack them up. - Yes, sir.
- مهلا، قم بحزمهم. - نعم سيدي.
Can we go out now?
هل يمكننا الخروج الآن؟
What was that?
ما هذا؟
These guys helped bring in the goods.
ساعد هؤلاء الأشخاص في نقل البضائع.
What should we do? They could be trouble if we leave them.
ماذا نفعل؟ قد يقعون في مشكلة إذا تركناهم.
Please don't kill us.
من فضلك لا تقتلنا.
We won't tell anyone what we saw here.
لن نخبر أحدًا بما رأيناه هنا.
Wouldn't it be better…
أليس هذا جيدا...
If they couldn't speak at all?
ماذا لو لم يتمكنوا من التحدث على الإطلاق؟
Nice and neat.
نظيفة وجميلة.
- I came to see my family. - Hey.
- جئت لرؤية عائلتي. - مرحبا.
- Please let me go. - You stink.
- دعني أذهب. - رائحتك كريهة.
Don't you have a family?
هل ليس لديك عائلة؟
Unfortunately, I don't.
للأسف، لا أفعل ذلك.
Even if I had one…
على الرغم من أن لدي واحدة…
Please spare me!
من فضلك ثق بي!
I would've killed them like I did just now.
سأقتلهم كما فعلت الآن.
Did I do something wrong again?
ماذا فعلت خطأ مرة أخرى؟
No.
لا
I did something wrong.
لقد فعلت شيئا خاطئا.
I should've just beaten you to death back then.
كان ينبغي لي أن أضربك حتى الموت حينها.
It's my fault.
إنه خطئي.
Your face tells me
وجهك يخبرني.
my counter punch landed pretty well.
لقد هبطت لكمتي بشكل جيد.
So it really was you.
إذن فهو أنت حقا.
Even a champion like you
حتى بطل مثلك.
should've been ready to take a hit or two once you entered the ring.
يجب أن تكون مستعدًا لتلقي ضربة أو اثنتين عند دخولك الحلبة.
Thanks.
شكرًا لك.
For what?
لماذا؟
For giving me a reason to beat the hell out of you
لأنك أعطيتني سببًا لأضربك بشدة.
without a second thought.
بدون تفكير ثانٍ.
I'm going to…
أنا سوف…
Kill you right here.
اقتلك هنا.
Hey.
يا.
Hey!
يا!
Where the hell did this punk go?
أين ذهب هذا الجحيم؟
119 EMERGENCY RESPONSE TEAM
فريق الاستجابة للطوارئ 119
Captain.
قائد الفريق.
I think I know where Dung-ju is.
أعتقد أنني أعرف أين يقع دونج جو.
What are you doing here after causing trouble?
ماذا تفعل هنا بعد التسبب في المشاكل؟
Do you know what you did?
هل تعلم ماذا فعلت؟
You need to control your temper.
يجب عليك التحكم بمشاعرك.
- Do you know what... - What?
- هل تعلم ماذا... - ماذا؟
What was I supposed to do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Hey.
يا.
Fortunately, she's going to make it.
لحسن الحظ أنها سوف تفعل ذلك.
But we'll have to wait and see when she'll wake up.
لكن علينا أن ننتظر ونرى عندما تستيقظ.
With no CCTVs in and out of the restaurant,
بدون كاميرات مراقبة داخل وخارج المطعم
it won't be easy to find out what exactly happened.
ليس من السهل معرفة ما حدث بالفعل.
We found traces of gunfire,
لقد وجدنا آثار إطلاق نار.
but your gun was clean with no fingerprints.
لكن مسدسك نظيف ، ولا يوجد عليه بصمات الأصابع.
We need to find evidence that Min Ju-yeong did it.
نحن بحاجة إلى العثور على دليل على أن مين جو يونغ فعلت ذلك.
But isn't it strange?
ولكن أليس هذا غريبا؟
The bullet went through the scapular artery.
لقد مرت الرصاصة من خلال الشريان الكتفي.
There would've been much blood loss.
سيكون هناك فقدان الكثير من الدم.
On top of that, it took 15 minutes for the ambulance to arrive
علاوة على ذلك، استغرق وصول سيارة الإسعاف 15 دقيقة .
after residents heard the gunshot and called it in.
وبعد أن سمع السكان إطلاق النار، اتصلوا مرة أخرى.
Under normal circumstances, she would've bled out in that time.
في الظروف العادية ، سوف تنزف خلال تلك الفترة.
According to the paramedics,
وهذا حسب تصريح الطبيب.
she had already received first aid by the time they arrived.
لقد تلقت بالفعل الإسعافات الأولية عندما وصلوا.
How's Min Ju-yeong?
كيف حالك مين جو يونغ؟
He got first aid at Insung University Hospital
تلقى الإسعافات الأولية في مستشفى جامعة إينسونغ.
and was admitted as an inpatient.
وتم إدخاله كمريض.
We'll need to wait for the test results,
علينا أن ننتظر نتائج الاختبار.
but his injuries seemed pretty severe.
لكن إصاباته تبدو خطيرة جدًا.
Take over the case from the local precinct.
أخرج هذه القضية من المنطقة.
Keep canvassing the area and trace Min Ju-yeong's movements.
استمر في مداهمة المنطقة وتتبع تحركات مين جو يونج.
And put out an APB for Kim Yeon-ha.
وأخرج APB لـ كيم يون ها.
- Yes, sir.
- نعم سيدي.
Multiple facial contusions,
العديد من الاصطدامات،
along with a number of lacerations and bruises.
إلى جانب بعض الكدمات والإصابات.
Total recovery time, 24 weeks.
فترة التعافي الإجمالية 24 أسبوعًا.
This is enough to be charged with aggravated assault.
وهذا يكفي لتوجيه تهمة التسبب في أذى جسدي خطير.
What happens now?
ماذا يحدث الآن؟
The ball is in Min Ju-yeong's court.
الكرة في ملعب مين جو يونغ.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
He has a video of Dong-ju assaulting him.
لديه فيديو لـ دونغ جو وهو يضربه.
Without appropriate disciplinary actions,
بدون اتخاذ إجراءات تأديبية مناسبة.
he'll make the video public.
سوف يجعل الفيديو علنيا.
And what does he mean by "appropriate disciplinary actions"?
وماذا يقصد بمصطلح "التأديب المناسب"؟
He wants Dong-ju relieved of his duties
يريد من دونغ جو أن يخفف من واجباته.
and the SCIT…
و SCIT…
Dissolved.
حل.
He wants to stop us from investigating further.
يريد أن يمنعنا من إجراء المزيد من التحقيق.
Everything was planned.
كل شيء مخطط له.
Everything from stealing the captain's gun to provoking Dong-ju.
كل شيء من سرقة بندقية القبطان إلى إثارة غضب دونغ جو.
I can cover for a simple gun misplacement,
أستطيع أن أغطي سوء وضع السلاح البسيط،
but not when there has been a casualty.
ولكن ليس عندما يكون هناك ضحايا.
I don't think you can avoid a demotion.
لا أعتقد أنه يمكنك تجنب ارتكاب الأخطاء.
And just like that, my lieutenant rank is gone.
هكذا فقط ، اختفت حالتي.
What did the commissioner say?
ماذا قال المفوض؟
This is a headache for him too.
وهذا يشكل صداعًا له أيضًا.
If that video goes public,
إذا كان الفيديو عامًا
he'll get in trouble since he created the SCIT.
سيكون في ورطة، لأنه أنشأ SCIT.
The nomination is right around the corner.
الترشيح قريب جدًا.
It seems he wants to handle this discreetly.
يبدو أنه يريد التعامل مع هذا الأمر بحذر.
Give it a few days until the disciplinary hearing.
أعطها بضعة أيام حتى جلسة الاستماع التأديبية.
He has a team dinner tonight, right?
لقد تناول عشاءً جماعيًا، أليس كذلك؟
RECRUITMENT &amp; SELECTION NOTICE: INVESTIGATION DIVISION POSITION
إشعار التوظيف والاختيار: وظيفة في قسم التحقيقات
- What are you staring at? - Hello, sir.
- ماذا تنظر إليه؟ - مرحبا سيدي.
I heard rumors of your team dissolving.
سمعت شائعات حول تفكك مجموعتك.
You must feel uneasy.
لا بد أنك تشعر بالحزن.
I mean, you switched teams to get promoted.
أعني أنك قمت بتغيير الفريق من أجل الترقية.
You can't catch a break, can you?
ألا يمكنك أن تأخذ استراحة؟
- Are you going home now? - No, there's a senior officials' dinner.
- هل ستذهب إلى المنزل الآن؟ - لا، هناك عشاء مسؤول كبير.
I bet he's going to put on a show tonight.
أراهن أنه سيكون في العرض الليلة.
Who do you mean?
من تقصد؟
Your captain.
قائد فريقك.
I hear he's bent on begging and pleading with the commissioner
سمعته ينحني ليتوسل ويطلب من المفوض.
to save that officer and your team.
لإنقاذ هذا الضابط وفريقك.
Man, I can't believe how that one officer ruined the team.
يا رجل، لا أستطيع أن أصدق كيف قام هذا الضابط بتدمير الفريق.
Why did he take that kid in anyway?
كيف يمكنه أن يأخذ هذا الطفل؟
Man-sik, par terre!
مان-سيك، على الأرض!
- You got this, sir! - Par terre.
- مفهوم يا سيدي! - على الأرض.
- Good luck, sir!
- حظا سعيدا يا سيدي!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
What do you think, punk?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I'm drinking.
انا اشرب.
You won't be relieved of your duties for now.
لن يتم إعفاؤك من مهامك في الوقت الحالي.
The disciplinary hearing or whatever will be held in a week.
سيتم عقد جلسة التأديب، أو ما شابه، في غضون أسبوع.
So make sure to prepare yourself.
لذلك تأكد من إعداد نفسك.
They'll take circumstances into account.
وسوف يأخذون الظروف بعين الاعتبار.
The commissioner is also aware of your situation.
والمفوض على علم أيضًا بحالتك.
You didn't have to do this!
لا يجب عليك فعل هذا!
Don't you raise your voice.
لا ترفع صوتك
Sit down and stop talking nonsense.
اجلس وتوقف عن التكلم بكلمات كاذبة.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I dragged you and the team into this mess.
لقد جررتك والفريق إلى هذه الفوضى.
I'll just quit.
سأتوقف.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تمزح.
Who said it was your fault?
من قال أن هذا خطؤك؟
It's my fault for not having enough power.
إنه خطئي لأنني لا أملك طاقة كافية.
I'm supposed to be the captain, but there's nothing I can do.
يجب أن أكون القائد، ولكن ليس هناك شيء أستطيع القيام به.
So I'm just trying to do whatever I can.
لذلك أحاول فقط أن أفعل ما بوسعي.
You did nothing wrong.
لم تفعل أي شيء خاطئ.
That bastard.
هذا الوحش.
Had I been in your shoes,
لو كنت في مكانك،
I would've beaten the hell out of him like my life depended on it too.
سأضربه ضربًا مبرحًا وكأن حياتي تعتمد على ذلك.
And what's this talk about quitting?
وماذا يقول هذا عن الاستسلام؟
If you quit,
إذا توقفت،
does that mean you'll let Min Ju-yeong off the hook?
هل هذا يعني أنك ستترك مين جو يونغ يفلت من العقاب؟
Jeez, you fool.
يا إلهي، أنت غبي.
You're a boxing champion and a national team athlete.
أنت بطل الملاكمة ولاعب وطني.
But you want to give up before the match is even over?
لكن هل تريد الاستسلام قبل انتهاء اللعبة؟
I bet Min Ju-yeong would love to hear all this.
أراهن أن مين جو يونغ سيحب سماع كل هذا.
Who said I was giving up?
من قال أني استسلمت؟
Exactly, so stop talking nonsense, all right?
إذن توقف عن الكلام الهراء ، حسنًا؟
You're a simple kid,
أنت فتى بسيط.
so don't overthink things, looking all serious.
لذلك لا تفكر كثيرًا ، وكن جادًا.
Hey, I've heard enough crap from you.
مهلا، لقد سمعت ما يكفي من الأكاذيب منك.
Come here and put this on me. I'm aching all over.
تعال هنا وضعيه عليّ. أنا في ألم في كل مكان.
Come on.
يأتي.
Jeez, that stings.
قالت جيس أن الأمر كان مخيفًا.
It stings!
قشعريرة!
What's this old handkerchief you always carry with you?
ما هو المنديل القديم الذي تحمله معك دائمًا؟
I can get you a new one.
أستطيع أن آخذ واحدة جديدة.
What?
ماذا؟
Hey, this is priceless.
مهلا، هذا لا يقدر بثمن.
My wife gave this to me
لقد أعطتني إياه زوجتي.
when she was pregnant with Jeong-a.
عندما كانت حاملاً بجونغ آ.
I won the bronze medal after she gave me this handkerchief.
لقد حصلت على الميدالية البرونزية بعد أن أعطتني هذا المنديل.
MAN-SIK, JEONG-A, JAE-GYEONG
مان سيك، جونغ آه، جاي جيونغ
- He held on! - He won the bronze medal!
- لقد صمد! - لقد فاز بالميدالية البرونزية!
- Jae-gyeong! - Go Man-sik of South Korea!
- جا هيونغ! - جو مان سيك من كوريا الجنوبية!
This is my lucky charm.
هذا هو حظي.
I know it doesn't look like it,
أعرف أن الأمر ليس كذلك.
but it's mine.
لكنها لي.
Hey, put more of that on the other side.
مهلا، ضع المزيد على الجانب الآخر.
I brought your stuff.
لقد أحضرت أغراضك.
See if anything's missing.
انظر إذا كان هناك أي شيء مفقود.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Nobody blames you.
لا أحد يلومك.
So don't make that face.
لذلك لا تصنع هذا الوجه.
It makes you look pathetic.
إنه يجعلك تبدو مثيرًا للشفقة.
But I ruined everything.
ولكنني دمرت كل شيء.
I'm no help at all.
ليس لدي أي مساعدة على الإطلاق.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Hey!
يا!
Our team hasn't been dissolved yet, so why are you apologizing?
لم يتم حل مجموعتنا بعد، فلماذا تعتذر؟
Seriously.
بجد.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
INSUNG METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
وكالة شرطة متروبوليتان إنسونغ
Things are a mess right now,
ماذا يحدث الآن؟
but we can't just sit back and do nothing.
ولكننا لا نستطيع الجلوس دون فعل شيء.
But there isn't much we can do at the moment.
ولكن ليس هناك الكثير مما يمكننا فعله الآن.
The outcome will be the same even if we stay put,
النتيجة ستبقى كما هي حتى لو استمرينا.
so we might as well do something.
حتى نتمكن من فعل شيء ما أيضًا.
But we need a lead to dig into the guy.
لكننا نحتاج إلى دليل للعثور على الرجل.
Excuse me.
آسف.
Here's the restored data from Min Ju-yeong's burner phone
هذه هي البيانات التي تم استردادها من الهاتف المحروق الخاص بـ Min Ju-yeong.
and Kim Yeon-ha's file.
ووثائق كيم يون ها.
The Ministry of Foreign Affairs confirmed that the passport was forged.
وأكدت وزارة الخارجية أن جواز السفر مزور.
In addition to Kim Yeon-ha,
بالإضافة إلى كيم يون ها
she has several fake identities of different nationalities.
لديها هويات مزيفة متعددة ، وجنسيات مختلفة.
Excuse me.
آسف.
Sir, how are you feeling?
كيف حالك يا معلم؟
Not great.
ليس رائعا.
Would you like me to help you feel better?
هل تريد مني أن أساعدك على الشعور بالتحسن؟
Many calls were made to the phone number registered under Kim Yeon-ha.
تم إجراء عدة مكالمات إلى رقم هاتف مسجل باسم كيم يون ها.
They seem pretty close.
يبدو أنهم قريبون جدًا.
Are you here to kill me?
هل أنت هنا لتقتلني؟
Why would I do that?
لماذا أفعل هذا؟
From the looks of you, I think someone else might do the job.
من وجهة نظرك ، أعتقد أن شخصًا آخر يمكنه القيام بهذه المهمة.
If you die,
إذا مت،
things will only get difficult for me.
ستكون الأمور صعبة بالنسبة لي.
There are a few other numbers he often called besides Kim Yeon-ha's.
هناك أرقام أخرى قليلة يتصل بها بشكل متكرر إلى جانب كيم يون ها.
If you catch the burner phone dealer,
إذا وجدت بائع هاتف، أحرقه.
you can identify the people Min Ju-yeong was in contact with.
يمكنك التعرف على الأشخاص الذين يتواصل معهم مين جو يونغ.
Most of the burner phones are registered to Russians and Chinese.
وكانت معظم الهواتف المحروقة مملوكة لمواطنين روس وصينيين.
What's going on? Why is he here?
ماذا حدث؟ لماذا هو هنا؟
When did this punk get here?
متى وصلت هذه الحديقة إلى هنا؟
What are you planning to trick our naive captain with this time?
ما هي خطتك لخداع قائدنا الغبي هذه المرة؟
Good point. Why share this all of a sudden?
نقطة جيدة. لماذا المشاركة فورًا؟
What are you up to now?
ماذا لديك الآن؟
I'm not that bad a person.
أنا لست شخصا سيئا.
I do feel bad about what happened.
أشعر بالسوء بسبب ما حدث.
Anyway, this is the best I can do to help.
ومع ذلك، هذا هو أفضل ما يمكنني فعله للمساعدة.
We'll keep an eye on Min Ju-yeong, so do what you can.
سوف نتابع مين جو يونغ، لذا افعل ما بوسعك.
Good luck. Bye.
حظا سعيدا. وداعا.
Senior Officers Shin and Ji, analyze this data.
يقوم الضابطان الكبيران شين وجي بتحليل هذه البيانات.
Sergeant Kim and I will find the burner phone dealer.
الرقيب كيم وأنا سوف نبحث عن بائع الهاتف المحترق.
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
- دعنا نذهب. - نعم سيدي.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
Hey, what about me?
مهلا، ماذا عني؟
Wait. What do you want me to do?
انتظر ماذا تريدني أن أفعل؟
Don't do anything.
لا تفعل شيئا.
Just stay put!
فقط ضعها!
- Stay with Ms. Jeong. - What?
- مع السيدة جونغ. - ماذا؟
But you told me not to give up.
ولكنك قلت لي أن لا أستسلم.
This is all my fault. Do you really expect me to stand by like an idiot?
هذا كله خطئي. هل تتوقع مني حقًا أن أقف مكتوف الأيدي؟
Yeah!
نعم!
I won't get in trouble again.
لن أواجه أي مشاكل أخرى.
I'll only do what you tell me to do.
سأفعل كل ما تطلب مني أن أفعله.
As if I can trust you.
كأنني أستطيع أن أثق بك.
Let's take him with us.
دعونا نأخذه معنا.
It's better to keep him with us than risk him causing trouble.
من الأفضل أن نبقيه معنا بدلاً من المخاطرة بتسببه في المشاكل.
Unless he's an idiot, he won't cause any more trouble.
إذا لم يكن أحمقًا ، فلن يسبب أي مشاكل أخرى.
I guess.
أعتقد ذلك.
Move, punk. Get in the car.
تحرك يا بانك. اركب السيارة.
Where will we find the burner phone dealer?
أين سنجد تاجر الهاتف المحروق؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I know just the person who can help us with that.
أنا أعرف فقط شخصًا يمكنه مساعدتنا في ذلك.
These are the texts Min Ju-yeong received right before he was arrested,
هذه هي الرسائل النصية التي تلقاها مين جو يونغ قبل اعتقاله.
but there's no way they were work-related.
ولكن لا توجد أي طريقة تربطهم بالعمل.
"Bonded warehouse 201."
"مستودع العقود 201".
It's a cold storage warehouse near Chinatown.
إنه مستودع تخزين بارد بالقرب من الحي الصيني.
It used to be run by the Golden Bunny Gang,
كانت تحت سيطرة عصابة الأرنب الذهبي في السابق،
and the manager was Lee Sang-su.
والمدير هو لي سانغ سو.
Lee Sang-su?
لي سانغ سو؟
Golden Bunny's younger brother, Silver Bunny?
الأخ الأصغر للأرنب الذهبي، براك باني؟
Yeah.
نعم.
The warehouse is shut down now, and Silver Bunny is still on the run.
تم الآن إغلاق المستودع ولا يزال Silver Bunny يعمل.
Kim Yeon-ha's arrival time was also 4:10 a.m.
موعد وصول كيم يون ها هو الساعة 4:10 صباحًا.
She departed from Manila, Philippines.
غادرت مانيلا، الفلبين.
"Filipino air cargo ETA, next day at 4:10 a.m."
"وقت الوصول المتوقع لشركة الشحن الجوي الفلبينية في اليوم التالي الساعة 4:10 صباحًا"
There's a Russian ship that arrived at Insung Port at 5 a.m.
وصلت سفينة روسية إلى ميناء إينسونغ في الساعة الخامسة صباحًا.
It's called the Victory.
ويسمى النصر.
It's owned by a shipping company
إنها تابعة للناقل.
that smuggled used cars and drug precursors.
من يقوم بتهريب السيارات المستعملة والمخدرات؟
"Russian sea cargo ETA, next day at 5 a.m."
"الموعد المتوقع لوصول الشحن البحري الروسي في اليوم التالي الساعة الخامسة صباحًا"
I wonder what came in.
أتساءل ماذا سيأتي.
Let's investigate the bonded warehouses in the Russian cargo sector.
دعونا نلقي نظرة على المستودعات الجمركية في قطاع الشحن الروسي.
Okay.
تمام.
Hey, be gentle. I got new hair transplanted there.
مرحباً أيها السادة، لقد حصلت على قصة شعر جديدة هناك.
That hurts a bit.
إنه يؤلمني قليلا.
Okay, that's good.
حسنًا، هذا جيد.
Hey, be careful.
مهلا، كن حذرا.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Damn it.
مكسور.
What do you want now?
ماذا تريد الآن؟
Jeez, you scared me.
يا إلهي، أنت تخيفني.
If the burner phone is registered under a Russian or Chinese name,
إذا كان الهاتف المحروق مسجلاً باسم روسي أو صيني.
there's only one go-to guy in Insung.
هناك ولد واحد فقط في إنسونغ.
Get off the bus!
انزل من الحافلة!
Burner phone dealers usually do business with tour guides.
عادةً ما يتعامل بائعو الهواتف المحترقة مع المرشدين السياحيين.
All right, everyone.
حسنا، الجميع.
They collect everyone's passports, saying that it's necessary
قاموا بجمع جوازات سفر الجميع ، قائلين أن ذلك ضروري.
- for hotel or tourist site reservations. - Okay, good job.
- لحجز الفنادق أو المعالم السياحية. - حسنًا، عمل جيد.
After they do that,
بعد أن فعلوا ذلك
they take photos of the passports to get information.
يقومون بأخذ صور جواز السفر للحصول على المعلومات.
CLEANING SUPPLY CLOSET
تنظيف منطقة العرض
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I told you to stay with the group.
لقد قلت لك أن تبقى مع الفريق.
Here, hold onto this. I can't get a good shot.
تمسك بهذا. لا أستطيع التصويب جيدًا.
No, back up a little.
لا، تراجع قليلا.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Who do you think? I'm a cop.
من تظنني؟ أنا ضابط شرطة.
A cop?
شرطة؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Hey, look at this.
مهلا، انظر إلى هذا.
You know who these people are, right?
هل تعرف من هم هؤلاء الأشخاص؟
They were in your tour group.
إنهم في مجموعتك السياحية.
You used their passports to make burner phones!
لقد استخدمت جواز سفرهم لصنع الهاتف!
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
All I did was take and send photos for 10,000 won each.
ما فعلته هو أنني قمت بالتقاط الصور وإرسالها مقابل 10000 وون لكل صورة.
So tell us what you know.
فأخبرنا بما تعرفه.
I just told you everything.
لقد أخبرتك بكل شيء.
I even gave you my phone.
حتى أنني اتصلت بك.
Who's Daepodong Number One?
من هو دايبودونج؟
The burner phone market's boss.
رئيس سوق الهواتف المحترق.
I don't know his real name. He just goes by Daepodong.
لا أعرف اسمه الحقيقي. هو فقط يذهب إلى دايبودونغ.
Where's that bastard?
أين هذا الأحمق؟
How should I know?
كيف يمكنني أن أعرف؟
I heard he was wanted by the police,
سمعت أنه تم القبض عليه من قبل الشرطة.
but I only met him once when I first started working.
ولكنني التقيت به مرة واحدة فقط ، عندما بدأت العمل لأول مرة.
I'm telling the truth. Hey, that hurts!
أنا أقول الحقيقة. مهلا، هذا يؤلمني!
No.
لا
That's not him.
هذا ليس هو.
No. It's not him.
لا، إنه ليس هو.
- Are you really looking? - I am.
- هل تبحث حقًا؟ - أنا.
No. Not him.
لا، ليس هو.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's keep at it until we find him.
فلنحتفظ به حتى نجده.
It's not him.
إنه ليس هو.
Not him.
ليس هو.
No…
لا…
You're not answering.
انت لا تجيب.
Are you sleepy?
هل انت نعسان؟
Next guy, please!
التالي من فضلك!
That isn't him.
هذا ليس هو.
Open your eyes!
افتح عينيك!
Okay!
تمام!
Sir, wake up.
سيدي، استيقظ.
Morning's here.
صباح الخير هنا.
It's not him.
إنه ليس هو.
We have to find our guy.
نحن بحاجة للعثور على رجلنا.
Toasted egg sandwiches are the best in the morning.
ساندويتش البيض المقلي هو الأفضل في الصباح.
- Everyone! - What?
-الجميع! -ماذا؟
I thought we could use a hearty breakfast.
أعتقد أننا قد نحتاج إلى وجبة إفطار لذيذة.
Please enjoy.
يتمتع.
- Here. - Thank you.
- هنا. - شكرا لك.
Here, Dung-ju.
وهنا دونج جو.
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Isn't Dung-ju pushing himself too hard?
دونغجو، هل تحاول جاهدا؟
It's not him.
إنه ليس هو.
- He pulled two all-nighters. - He can do two more.
- لقد سحب شخصين طوال الليل. - كان بإمكانه أن يفعل اثنين آخرين.
- Detective? - Yes?
- محقق؟ - نعم؟
I'm too hungry to focus.
أنا جائع جدًا ولا أستطيع التركيز.
Can I have some food before we continue?
هل يمكنني تناول بعض الطعام قبل أن نستمر؟
- Do you want it? - Yes.
- هل تريدها؟ - نعم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Hey, it's this person!
مهلا، هذا هو الشخص!
This is him! Daepodong!
هذا هو! ديبوتونج!
Daepodong!
مستودع!
- Are you sure? - I am. It's Daepodong.
- هل أنت متأكد؟ - أنا متأكد. إنه دايبودونغ.
Not Nam Po-dong, the actor?
أليس هذا نام بو دونغ؟
Not Nam Po-dong! It's Daepodong!
ليس نامبودونغ! إنه دايبودونغ!
I found you, Daepodong.
لقد وجدتك دايبودونج.
Don't come after me!
لا تأتي ورائي!
- Calm down and open the door. - I don't do that kind of stuff anymore.
- اصمت وافتح الباب. - لن أفعل هذا النوع من الأشياء مرة أخرى.
Holy crap!
فروي!
Don't you know Daepodong Number One?
هل تعرف دايبودونغ رقم ​​واحد؟
I can't believe he's only 32 years old.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنه يبلغ من العمر 32 عامًا فقط.
This guy is Daepodong Number One?
هل هذا الرجل هو دايبودونج رقم واحد؟
I've never seen him before!
لم أره من قبل!
So you've never met the warehouse owner, and they've been out of business?
إذن لم تقابل مالك المستودع أبدًا وخرج من العمل؟
No, I have no idea.
لا، ليس لدي أي فكرة.
- Go, Commissioner!
- اذهب يا مفوض!
- You're so strong, sir!
- أنت قوي جدًا يا سيدي!
Have you heard anything about the Russian mafia around here?
هل سمعت عن المافيا الروسية هنا؟
Who are you guys?
من أنت؟
Just a second.
ثانية واحدة.
I swear I'm not in that business anymore. I live an honest life!
أقسم أنني لم أعد في هذا المجال. أعيش بصدق!
Okay, fine.
تمام.
Do you know this person?
هل تعرف هذا الشخص؟
No, I don't.
لا أنا لا.
I'd remember him if I had seen that face.
سأتذكره إذا رأيت هذا الوجه.
MAN-SIK, JEONG-A, JAE-GYEONG
مان سيك، جونغ آه، جاي جيونغ
If you die,
إذا مت،
things will only get difficult for me.
ستكون الأمور صعبة بالنسبة لي.
Or do you want to tell me
أو تريد أن تخبرني؟
where I can find that bitch?
أين يمكنني العثور على تلك العاهرة؟
What do you say?
ماذا تقول؟
If I tell you…
إذا قلت لك...
It'll make things difficult for me.
سيجعل الأمور صعبة بالنسبة لي.
Make the goods, and I'll tell you then.
قم بالتسوق، سأخبرك حينها.
You really are a bad boy.
أنت فتى سيء حقًا.
Here's your vitamin.
هذا هو فيتامينك.
About the lady from the noodle place.
عن الفتاة من محل المعكرونة.
I wonder how she survived.
أتساءل كيف تنجو.
By all accounts, she should've died.
على كل حال، كان ينبغي لها أن تموت.
Can I get you something?
هل يمكنني أن أحضر لك شيئا؟
Damn it.
مكسور.
RECENT CALLS
المكالمات الأخيرة
DONG-JU
دونغ جو
Don't do that.
لا تفعل ذلك.
People might think I'm a gang boss or something.
قد يعتقد الناس أنني زعيم عصابة أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
Yes, sir.
نعم.
Will you be heading home?
هل انت ذاهب الى المنزل؟
No, I want to buy some fruit.
لا، أريد شراء بعض الفاكهة.
WANTED: JANG CHUNG-GI (DAEPODONG)
مطلوب: جانج تشونغ جي (داي إيبودونج)
Find anything?
ما الذي تبحث عنه؟
Man, I'm exhausted.
يا رجل، أنا متعب.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
Everyone looks exhausted.
يبدو أن الجميع مرهقون.
Here, try it.
هنا، جربه.
On your shoulders like this.
على كتفك مثل هذا.
- Hey, that feels good. - Good.
- مهلا، هذا يشعرني بالارتياح. - جيد.
They're starting to loosen up.
لقد بدأوا بالاسترخاء.
Your shoulders will feel better.
سوف تشعر بالارتياح في كتفيك.
LEE JONG-HUN
لي جونغ هون
Hey, what is it?
مهلا، ما الأمر؟
Hey!
يا!
What the hell are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Stop it.
اوقفها.
What a rude way to greet a visitor.
ما هذه الطريقة الوقحة لاستقبال الضيف.
She's badly injured.
لقد أصيبت بجروح خطيرة.
I guess she can't have these.
لا أعتقد أنها تستطيع الحصول على هذه الأشياء.
The two of you should enjoy them instead.
ينبغي لكما أن تكونا سعيدين من أجلهما.
Are you kidding me?
هل أنت تمزح؟
I brought them as a gesture of goodwill.
لقد أحضرتهم كبادرة حسن نية.
You shot a person, and you speak of goodwill?
لقد أطلقت النار على شخص وتحدثت عن حسن النية؟
You need another beating?
هل تحتاج إلى الضرب مرة أخرى؟
There you go again.
ها أنت ذا مرة أخرى.
Accusing me without evidence or witnesses.
إتهامي بدون دليل أو شهود.
Don't you agree?
ألا توافق؟
Or maybe…
أو ربما…
That lady saw me.
لقد رأتني المرأة.
I see you're injured.
أرى أنك مصاب.
It happens when you hold a handgun incorrectly.
يحدث هذا عندما تحمل السلاح بطريقة غير صحيحة.
Especially for someone inexperienced, just like yourself.
وخاصة بالنسبة للأشخاص عديمي الخبرة مثلك.
You got me.
لقد حصلت علي.
But does this count as evidence?
ولكن هل يعتبر هذا دليلا؟
If she wakes, tell her this.
إذا استيقظت أخبرها.
Although it's unlikely that she saw her shooter,
رغم أنه من غير المرجح أن تكون قد رأت الشخص الذي أطلق عليها النار.
even if she did,
على الرغم من أنها فعلت ذلك،
she should stay quiet.
ينبغي لها أن تكون هادئة.
If not, who knows what might happen?
إذا كنت لا تعرف ماذا يمكن أن يحدث؟
Do whatever you want.
افعل ما تريد
I'm going to have you locked up, no matter what.
سأقوم بإغلاقك، لا مشكلة.
You scumbag asshole.
أنت مجنون، وداعا.
Are you going to fight for justice or something?
هل ستقاتل من أجل العدالة أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Don't even dream about it.
لا تحلم بذلك حتى.
The law, rules, fair play…
القانون، القانون، العدالة...
All that crap is only relevant in your boxing ring.
كل ذلك له أهمية فقط في حلبة الملاكمة الخاصة بك.
That kind of bullshit doesn't fly in my streets.
مثل هذه الأفعال الشريرة لا تطير في شارعي.
Don't you get it?
ألا تفهم ذلك؟
You bastard.
أنت غبية.
I said stop it.
قلت توقف.
You should stop as well and go.
ينبغي عليك التوقف والذهاب.
When you have time, please teach me…
عندما يكون لديك الوقت، من فضلك علمني...
How to shoot a gun.
كيفية اطلاق النار بالبندقية.
I'd like to make sure to hit my mark next time.
أريد التأكد من أنني سأحصل على نقاطي في المرة القادمة.
Goddammit!
يا إلهي!
Excuse me.
آسف.
You forgot to take this.
لقد نسيت أن تحضر هذا.
What a shame.
يا للعار.
It looks like nobody saw that.
يبدو أن لا أحد رأى ذلك.
Here. Get your vitamins in.
هنا. احصل على الفيتامينات الخاصة بك.
It'll help with your recovery.
وسوف يساعدك على التعافي.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I just like you.
انا معجب بك فقط.
- What do you mean? - How can I not like someone so cool?
- ماذا تقصد؟ - لماذا لا تحب الأشخاص الرائعين؟
It's your fault.
إنه خطؤك.
Stop staring.
توقف عن النظر.
Mr. Yoon Dong-ju?
السيد يون دونغ جو؟
Can I have a word with you?
هل يمكنني التحدث معك؟
If you keep this up, the bones won't heal properly,
إذا استمر هذا الوضع، فلن يشفى العظم.
and it'll leave your hand stuck like this.
وسوف تترك يديك عالقة بهذا الشكل.
Would you be able to use it properly then?
هل يمكنك استخدامه بشكل صحيح؟
Why would you say that, Doctor?
لماذا تقول ذلك يا دكتور؟
I'm telling the truth.
انا أقول الحقيقة.
You're not one to listen, are you?
أنت لست مستمعًا، أليس كذلك؟
Since you're here, let's do an MRI scan.
بما أنك هنا، دعنا نقوم بإجراء فحص التصوير بالرنين المغناطيسي.
A head MRI.
تصوير بالرنين المغناطيسي للرأس.
What did the doctor say?
ماذا قال الطبيب؟
What?
ماذا؟
Oh, nothing.
أوه، لا شيء.
He said my hand could end up looking like this,
قال أن يدي قد تبدو بهذا الشكل.
so I should be careful.
لذا يجب أن أكون حذرا.
What?
ماذا؟
Seriously?
بجد؟
That was it?
هذا كل شيء؟
I know, right?
أنا أوافق؟
He's a funny guy.
إنه شخص مضحك.
There he is. It's Daepodong.
ها هو ذا. إنه دايبودونغ.
You should go to Cheongpo-dong.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب إلى تشيونجبو دونج.
From what I've heard, he shows up there often.
من ما سمعته ، فهو يظهر هناك في كثير من الأحيان.
- Daepodong? - Yes?
- مستودع؟ -نعم؟
Oh, no!
أوه!
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
What are you doing? What's wrong?
ماذا تفعل؟ ما الخطب؟
It's nothing. Let's go.
لا شيء. هيا بنا.
Captain, I found them.
يا كابتن، لقد وجدتهم.
Even the records of people who called Min Ju-yeong's burner phone.
حتى سجلات الأشخاص الذين اتصلوا على هاتف مين جو يونغ تم حرقها.
You know Min Ju-yeong, the customs officer, right?
هل تعرف مين جو يونغ، ضابط الجمارك؟
I can't say.
لا أستطيع التحدث.
I don't really know any civil servants.
لا أعرف الكثير عن الموظفين المدنيين.
And what kind of a civil servant in Korea
وكيف هي حال الموظفين الحكوميين في كوريا؟
uses a burner phone?
استخدام الهاتف المحترق؟
There's a bastard who does.
هناك بعض الناس الأغبياء الذين يفعلون ذلك.
Let's get your wheels turning.
دعونا ندير عجلاتك.
Okay, then.
تمام.
Who did you sell those burner phones to?
من الذي بعت له تلك الهواتف المحروقة؟
If I tell you, I'll die.
إذا قلت لك سأموت.
Oh, I see.
أوه، أرى.
And who'd come after you?
ومن سيأتي بعدك؟
Okay, I'll tell you!
حسنا سأخبرك!
Just calm down.
فقط كن هادئا.
Every week,
كل اسبوع
some Korean Chinese guys come and buy them in bulk.
يأتي بعض الصينيين والكوريين للشراء بكميات كبيرة.
- Korean Chinese? - Yes.
- كوري، صيني؟ - نعم.
Have you heard of Baek?
هل سمعت عن بايك؟
Call him up. I want to see him.
اتصل به، أريد رؤيته.
You want me to call?
هل تريد مني أن أتصل؟
Yeah.
نعم.
They're really scary people.
إنهم أشخاص مخيفون حقًا.
You're just going to see his face, right?
فقط أنظر إلى وجهه، أليس كذلك؟
Worry about yourself.
لا تقلق بشأن نفسك.
What the heck? Let me go!
ماذا؟ دعني أذهب!
Our Father, who art in heaven,
أبانا الذي في السموات،
Hallowed be thy name.
من فضلك أعطه اسمك.
Thy kingdom come,
لتأت ملكوتك.
Thy will be done in earth, as it is in heaven.
إن إرادته تتم على الأرض كما هي في السماء.
I'm sorry, sir!
عذرا سيدي!
I didn't mean to snitch,
لا أقصد السرقة
but I had to because of the cops.
لكن يجب علي أن أفعل ذلك بسبب الشرطة.
If I'd known it was connected to you, I wouldn't have said anything.
لو كنت أعلم أن الأمر يتعلق بك، فلن أقول أي شيء.
I'll stay out of sight and live quietly.
سأبقى بعيدًا عن الأنظار وأعيش بهدوء.
And lead us not into temptation,
ولا تدخلنا في تجربة.
but deliver us from evil.
ولكن نجنا من الشرير.
Through the blood of the cross, grant us forgiveness.
بدم الصليب، امنحنا المغفرة.
It's been abandoned for a while.
لقد تم التخلي عنه لفترة من الوقت.
Will we find any traces of them?
هل سنعثر على آثارهم؟
If we don't find anything here,
إذا لم نجد أي شيء هنا
we'll search the port warehouse in Gyosa-dong.
سوف نجد مستودع الميناء في جيوسا دونج.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- دعنا نذهب. - حسنًا.
You're driving?
هل انت تقود؟
Yes. Why?
نعم. لماذا؟
Hold on a second.
إنتظر لمدة ثانية.
Is it that car?
هل هذه السيارة؟
This is Senior Officer Shin Jae-Hong of the SCIT.
هذا هو شين جاي هونغ، أحد كبار المسؤولين في SCIT.
Please run the plate number 25J 8405.
يرجى تشغيل لوحة الترخيص 25J 8405.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
It's unregistered.
لم يتم تسجيله.
Step on it.
خطوة عليها.
I think they're on to us. Who are they?
أعتقد أنهم في صفنا. من هم؟
We'll know when we catch them. Hold on tight.
سنعرف عندما نقبض عليهم. تمسك بهم جيدًا.
He has a gun!
لقد كان لديه مسدس!
Duck!
بطة!
He shot at us!
لقد أطلق النار علينا!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Those bastards.
هؤلاء الأوغاد.
Look at this.
أنظر إلى هذا.
- Keep up the good work. - Yes, sir.
-استمر في العمل الجيد. -نعم سيدي.
He's coming this way.
لقد جاء بهذه الطريقة.
He united Korean Chinese gangs from the three Northeastern Provinces
قام بتوحيد مجموعة من الشباب الصينيين الكوريين من المقاطعات الثلاث الشمالية الشرقية.
to form the Northeastern Syndicate
لإنشاء مجموعة الشمال الشرقي
and took over Chinatown, which used to be Golden Bunny's territory.
واستولى على الحي الصيني ، الذي كان في السابق أرض الأرنب الذهبي.
Introducing…
يوصي…
Baek Seok-chun, also known as Baek.
بايك سوك تشون معروف باسم بايك.
My brother will kill you.
أخي سوف يقتلك.
Open wide. It'll be over soon.
افتح الباب على مصراعيه. سينتهي الأمر قريبًا.
The rental warehouse was run by the mafia operating in the Russian Far East
يتم إدارة المستودع المستأجر من قبل مجموعة مافيا تعمل في الشرق الأقصى الروسي.
including Sakhalin and Khabarovsk.
بما في ذلك سخالين وخاباروفسك.
It looks like they came to Korea on a ship recently.
មើលទៅពួកគេមកកូរ៉េ នៅលើកប៉ាល់ថ្មីៗនេះ។
We have no intel on the boss's description or identity.
យើងមិនមាន intel លើការពិពណ៌នា ឬអត្តសញ្ញាណរបស់ចៅហ្វាយនោះទេ។
My mother's homeland.
មាតុភូមិកំណើតរបស់ខ្ញុំ។
The one who controls the drug supply across Korea, Japan, and Southeast Asia
អ្នកដែលគ្រប់គ្រងការផ្គត់ផ្គង់ថ្នាំ នៅទូទាំងប្រទេសកូរ៉េ ជប៉ុន និងអាស៊ីអាគ្នេយ៍
is Drug Monster, also known as Drugmon.
គឺ​ជា​បិសាច​គ្រឿងញៀន ដែល​ត្រូវ​បាន​គេ​ស្គាល់​ផង​ដែរ​ថា​ជា Drugmon ។
She came to Korea under the false identity of Kim Yeon-ha,
នាងមកកូរ៉េ ក្រោមអត្តសញ្ញាណក្លែងក្លាយរបស់ Kim Yeon-ha,
and she's wanted by Interpol and the police agency.
ហើយនាងត្រូវបាន Interpol និងភ្នាក់ងារប៉ូលីសចង់បាន។
Then there's Oh Jong-go, the CEO of J9 Security.
បន្ទាប់មកមានលោក Oh Jong-go ដែល ជានាយកប្រតិបត្តិនៃ J9 Security ។
And the person at the center of it all
ហើយមនុស្សនៅចំកណ្តាលរបស់វា។
is the Grade 7 customs officer,
ជាមន្ត្រីគយថ្នាក់ទី៧,
Min Ju-yeong.
មីន ជូយ៉ុង។
They're all expanding their profits through smuggling.
ពួកគេទាំងអស់កំពុងពង្រីកប្រាក់ចំណេញរបស់ពួកគេ តាមរយៈការរត់ពន្ធ។
Gangs, drugs, smuggling, and mafias.
ក្រុមក្មេងទំនើង គ្រឿងញៀន ការរត់ពន្ធ និងក្រុមម៉ាហ្វីយ៉ា។
It's a cartel of evil.
វាជាក្រុមនៃអំពើអាក្រក់។
This is what we've figured out so far.
នេះជាអ្វីដែលយើងបានគិតមកដល់ពេលនេះ។
If we look into the suborganizations,
បើយើងក្រឡេកមើលស្ថាប័នរង
we'll likely find most of the criminal groups in Insung.
យើងទំនងជានឹងរកឃើញ ក្រុមឧក្រិដ្ឋជនភាគច្រើននៅក្នុង Insung ។
This is intense.
នេះគឺខ្លាំង។
Can we handle this case?
តើយើងអាចដោះស្រាយករណីនេះបានទេ?
We'll need at least a few months to investigate.
យើងនឹងត្រូវការយ៉ាងហោចណាស់ ពីរបីខែដើម្បីស៊ើបអង្កេត។
Will our team still be around by then?
តើ​ក្រុម​របស់​យើង​នឹង​នៅ​ក្បែរ​នោះ​ទេ?
He probably has the commissioner in his pocket too.
គាត់ប្រហែលជាមានស្នងការ នៅក្នុងហោប៉ៅរបស់គាត់ផងដែរ។
We can't exactly investigate openly.
យើង​មិន​អាច​ស៊ើប​អង្កេត​ដោយ​ចំហ​ទេ។
Cops shouldn't be worried about authority when catching bad guys.
សមត្ថកិច្ច​មិន​គួរ​ព្រួយ​បារម្ភ​ពី​សមត្ថកិច្ច ​ពេល​ចាប់​មនុស្ស​អាក្រក់​នោះ​ទេ។
Bad guys need to get arrested.
មនុស្សអាក្រក់ត្រូវតែចាប់ខ្លួន។
- Hello, Commissioner! - Hello, sir!
-ជំរាបសួរលោកស្នងការ! -ជំរាបសួរលោក!
- Were you on night duty? - Jae-Hong!
- តើអ្នកបានបំពេញកាតព្វកិច្ចពេលយប់ទេ? - ជេ-ហុង!
- Hello, sir! - Hello, sir.
-ជំរាបសួរលោក! - ជំរាបសួរលោក។
What were you doing?
តើអ្នកកំពុងធ្វើអ្វី?
We were reflecting on our poor behavior, sir.
យើងកំពុងឆ្លុះបញ្ចាំងពី អាកប្បកិរិយាមិនល្អរបស់យើង លោកម្ចាស់។
That's what we've been doing, right?
នោះហើយជាអ្វីដែលយើងកំពុងធ្វើមែនទេ?
I was working out, sir.
ខ្ញុំ​កំពុង​តែ​ធ្វើ​ការ​ហើយ​លោក​ម្ចាស់។
You sure do look like a troublemaker.
អ្នកប្រាកដជាមើលទៅដូចជាអ្នកបង្កបញ្ហា។
You never do as you're told, do you?
អ្នកមិនដែលធ្វើដូចគេប្រាប់ទេ?
- Landscape mode. - Portrait is the trend, sir.
- របៀបទេសភាព។ - រូបបញ្ឈរគឺជានិន្នាការ។
He's been looking for a way to recover his dropping social media views.
គាត់កំពុងស្វែងរកមធ្យោបាយដើម្បីស្ដារឡើងវិញនូវ ទិដ្ឋភាពប្រព័ន្ធផ្សព្វផ្សាយសង្គមដែលធ្លាក់ចុះរបស់គាត់។
By the way, it appears that the SCIT
ដោយវិធីនេះវាលេចឡើងថា SCIT
will be dissolved within a week.
នឹងត្រូវរំលាយក្នុងរយៈពេលមួយសប្តាហ៍។
He'll be helping out instead of Golden Bunny from now on.
គាត់នឹងជួយ ជំនួស Golden Bunny ចាប់ពីពេលនេះតទៅ។
Introduce yourselves.
ណែនាំខ្លួនអ្នក។
Yes, sir.
نعم.
I'm Oh Jong-go.
ខ្ញុំគឺ Oh Jong-go។
I run a small security firm and a logistics company.
ខ្ញុំបើកក្រុមហ៊ុនសន្តិសុខតូចមួយ និងក្រុមហ៊ុនដឹកជញ្ជូន។
And I was…
ហើយខ្ញុំគឺ…
A heavyweight boxing champion.
ជើងឯកប្រដាល់ទម្ងន់ធ្ងន់។
Take a seat.
អង្គុយ។
Yes, sir.
نعم.
By the way,
ដោយវិធីនេះ,
did you find the bastards who stole my Candy precursors?
តើ​អ្នក​បាន​រក​ឃើញ​មនុស្ស​តិរច្ឆាន ​ដែល​លួច​ស្ករ​គ្រាប់​មុន​គេ​របស់​ខ្ញុំ​ទេ?
There were more than just a couple.
មាន​ច្រើន​ជាង​ប្ដី​ប្រពន្ធ។
The mayor's son got hooked on Candy and crossed the line.
កូនប្រុសរបស់អភិបាលក្រុងបានជាប់នឹងស្ករគ្រាប់ ហើយបានឆ្លងផ្លូវ។
The remaining precursors will be collected soon.
មុនគេដែលនៅសល់ នឹងត្រូវប្រមូលក្នុងពេលឆាប់ៗនេះ។
Hey, Mr. Min.
លោក មីន។
Why is everything a mess?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្វីៗទាំងអស់រញ៉េរញ៉ៃ?
The bunny bastard is in jail,
កូនទន្សាយជាប់គុក
and the bribed mayor's son is making a shitshow.
ហើយកូនប្រុសរបស់អភិបាលក្រុងដែលត្រូវបានសូកប៉ាន់ កំពុងធ្វើរឿងអាស្រូវ។
And the cops are swarming in like flies because of that shitshow.
ហើយ​សមត្ថកិច្ច​កំពុង​ចោមរោម​ដូច​សត្វ​រុយ ​ដោយសារ​រឿង​អាស្រូវ​នោះ។
At this rate, this place may be left unfinished as is.
ក្នុងអត្រានេះ កន្លែងនេះអាចនឹងត្រូវបានទុកចោលមិនទាន់ចប់សព្វគ្រប់។
That won't happen.
វានឹងមិនកើតឡើងទេ។
This is our starting point.
នេះគឺជាចំណុចចាប់ផ្តើមរបស់យើង។
It can't fall apart already.
វា​មិន​អាច​ដាច់​បាន​ហើយ។
Can you swear to God on that?
តើអ្នកអាចស្បថចំពោះព្រះលើរឿងនោះបានទេ?
I want my trust in partners to be bulletproof.
أريد أن أثق في شريكي لحمايتي من الرصاص.
My mother told me not to trust others so easily.
قالت لي والدتي أن لا أثق بالآخرين بسهولة.
I swear.
أقسم.
Is this good enough?
هل هذا جيد بما فيه الكفاية؟
You…
أنت…
Shouldn't trust me.
لا يجب عليك أن تصدقني.
Don't trust me. Trust money.
لا تثق بي. ثق بالمال.
Trust the unimaginable amount of money that will fall into your laps.
ثق في المبلغ غير المتوقع من المال الذي سيقع في دائرتك.
"Though thy beginning was small…."
"حتى لو كانت بدايتك صغيرة..."
"Yet thy latter end should greatly increase."
"ولكن ينبغي أن يزيد صافي أرباحك بشكل كبير."
- Captain, can I... - Go home.
- يا كابتن، هل يمكنني... - العودة إلى المنزل.
So do we…
فماذا لو...
Just sit back and do nothing?
الجلوس دون فعل شيء؟
I wish we could do something.
أتمنى أن نتمكن من فعل شيء ما.
What's going to happen now?
ماذا سيحدث الآن؟
Say something!
أخبرني قصة!
Do you even need to ask?
هل تحتاج إلى السؤال؟
This is it for us.
هذا لنا.
The team will get dissolved.
سيتم حل المجموعة.
We'll all face disciplinary action.
سوف نواجه جميعا عقوبات.
Then we'll return to our respective positions.
ثم نعود إلى مواقفنا الخاصة.
We will now begin the disciplinary hearing
سنبدأ الآن جلسة الاستماع التأديبية.
regarding the dismissal of Officer Yoon Dong-ju.
بخصوص إقالة الضابط يون دونغ جو.
Anything to say before we begin?
هل هناك أي شيء تريد قوله قبل أن نبدأ؟
Dung-ju's disciplinary hearing probably started.
ربما بدأت جلسة الاستماع التأديبية لدونغجو .
I hope he's doing okay in there.
آمل أن يكون بخير هناك.
He'll be lucky if he only gets suspended.
سيكون محظوظا لو تم إيقافه فقط.
Officer Yoon Dong-ju?
الضابط يون دونغ جو؟
That's how it'll end.
وهكذا سينتهي الأمر.
The bad guys will go on living without a care,
الأشخاص السيئون سيستمرون في العيش دون اهتمام.
while the dead are left with injustice.
في حين أن الموتى يُترَكون ظلماً.
Are you going to fight for justice or something?
هل ستقاتل من أجل العدالة أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Don't even dream about it.
لا تحلم بذلك حتى.
The law, rules, fair play…
القانون، القانون، العدالة...
All that crap is only relevant in your boxing ring.
كل ذلك له أهمية فقط في حلبة الملاكمة الخاصة بك.
That kind of bullshit doesn't fly in my streets.
مثل هذه الأفعال الشريرة لا تطير في شارعي.
On behalf of all the athletes,
بالنيابة عن جميع اللاعبين
I hereby pledge
أعدك.
to compete with honor and a true spirit of sportsmanship,
التنافس بالشرف والروح الرياضية الحقيقية.
respecting and abiding by the rules.
احترم القانون وأطيعه.
Athletes' representative, Yoon Dong-ju.
الممثل الرياضي يون دونغ جو.
Officer Yoon Dong-ju, please sit...
الضابط يون دونغ جو، من فضلك اجلس...
Officer Yoon!
الضابط يون!
What?
ماذا؟
Then where the heck is he right now?
فأين هو الآن؟
How can I...
هل يمكنني...
We need to talk.
نحن بحاجة للتحدث.
His last visit to the hospital was three days ago.
زيارته الأخيرة للمستشفى كانت منذ ثلاثة أيام.
If he's not in the on-call room or at the hospital, then where is he?
إذا لم يكن في غرفة الاتصال أو في المستشفى، أين هو؟
We haven't been able to reach him for two days now.
لم نتمكن من الوصول إليه لمدة يومين.
Are you sure Dong-ju last met with Oh Jong-go?
هل أنت متأكد أن دونغ جو التقى بأوه جونغ جو في المرة الأخيرة؟
Yes, I checked with the female bookkeeper.
نعم، لقد تأكدت من ذلك مع المرأة التي ألفت الكتاب.
We can't reach Oh Jong-go either.
نحن لا نستطيع الوصول إلى أوه جونغ-جو أيضًا.
She says he's on a business trip, but she doesn't know where he is.
تقول أنه مسافر في رحلة عمل، لكنها لا تعرف أين هو.
Do you think…
هل تعتقد…
Dung-ju got himself into big trouble?
دونغجو في ورطة كبيرة؟
I don't know, damn it!
لا أعرف!
What about Min Ju-yeong?
ماذا عن مين جو يونغ؟
He took a sick leave and went on vacation after getting discharged,
حصل على إجازة مرضية وذهب في إجازة بعد خروجه من المستشفى.
but we can't locate him.
ولكننا لا نستطيع العثور عليه.
Where the hell is Dung-ju holed up?
أين يقع دونج جو عالقا؟
I'll go and check out
سأذهب للتحقق.
a gym in Dongho-dong where Dung-ju used to go.
كانت صالة الألعاب الرياضية في دونغهو دونغ هي المكان الذي اعتاد دونغ جو الذهاب إليه.
In any case, once we locate Oh Jong-go and Min Ju-yeong…
ومع ذلك، عندما نجد أوه جونغ-غو ومين جو-يونغ...
- What the heck? - What is it?
- ماذا؟ - ما هو؟
It's moving.
إنه يتحرك.
You scared me, you little bastard!
أنت خائف مني، يا جرو!
What are you doing there? Come out!
ماذا تفعل هناك؟ اخرج!
For crying out loud, you idiot!
أصرخ بصوت عالي أيها الأحمق!
What happened to your face? Let me see.
ماذا حدث لوجهك؟ دعني أرى.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
You got into trouble again, didn't you?
هل تواجه مشاكل مرة أخرى؟
I spent the weekend going around looking for you!
لقد قضيت عطلة نهاية الأسبوع في البحث عنك!
I didn't get into trouble.
ខ្ញុំ​មិន​មាន​បញ្ហា​ទេ។
I just thought I should do something.
ខ្ញុំគ្រាន់តែគិតថាខ្ញុំគួរធ្វើអ្វីមួយ។
So you went to Oh Jong-go to settle things once and for all?
អញ្ចឹងអ្នកទៅ Oh Jong-go ដើម្បីដោះស្រាយរឿងម្តងហើយឬនៅ?
To get a confession from him?
ដើម្បីទទួលបានចម្លើយសារភាពពីគាត់?
I can't believe you, Dung-ju.
ខ្ញុំ​មិន​អាច​ជឿ​អ្នក​បាន​ទេ Dung-ju ។
You little brat!
កូនពៅអើយ!
You couldn't help yourself and had to get into a fight, didn't you?
អ្នក​មិន​អាច​ជួយ​ខ្លួន​ឯង​បាន ហើយ​ត្រូវ​ចូល​ទៅ​ក្នុង​ការ​ប្រយុទ្ធ​គ្នា​មែន​ទេ?
Why can't you see that this accomplishes nothing?
ហេតុ​អ្វី​បាន​ជា​អ្នក​មើល​មិន​ឃើញ ​ថា​ការ​នេះ​មិន​បាន​សម្រេច​អ្វី​មួយ?
Man, this is frustrating!
បុរស​នេះ​ហួស​ចិត្ត​!
Why are you following me?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នកតាមខ្ញុំ?
INSUNG SUPERMARKET
ផ្សារទំនើបអ៊ីនស៊ុង
Here.
នៅទីនេះ។
I don't have anywhere to go.
ខ្ញុំមិនមានកន្លែងណាដែលត្រូវទៅទេ។
Can I stay with you?
តើខ្ញុំអាចនៅជាមួយអ្នកបានទេ?
Are you always like this?
តើអ្នកតែងតែបែបនេះទេ?
What?
អ្វី?
I guess I somewhat knew, but you're beyond help.
ខ្ញុំគិតថាខ្ញុំដឹងខ្លះហើយ ប៉ុន្តែអ្នកលើសពីជំនួយ។
You think it's okay to ignore the problem and laugh things off, right?
អ្នកគិតថាវាមិនអីទេក្នុងការព្រងើយកន្តើយនឹងបញ្ហា ហើយសើចចេញមែនទេ?
Just go.
គ្រាន់តែទៅ។
I was an idiot to think you were decent.
ខ្ញុំជាមនុស្សល្ងង់ដែលគិតថាអ្នកសមរម្យ។
RICE PORRIDGE
បបរអង្ករ
This pitiful act doesn't suit you.
ទង្វើដ៏គួរឲ្យអាណិតនេះមិនសមនឹងអ្នកទេ។
Where on earth are you staying, you punk?
តើអ្នកស្នាក់នៅលើផែនដីនេះនៅឯណា?
Dung-ju looked pretty bad.
Dung-ju មើលទៅអាក្រក់ណាស់។
Do you think the other person got hurt badly too?
តើ​អ្នក​គិត​ថា​អ្នក​ដ៏​ទៃ ​ក៏​ឈឺ​យ៉ាង​ខ្លាំង​ដែរ​ឬ​ទេ?
What do you mean?
តើអ្នកចង់មានន័យដូចម្តេច?
The commissioner decided to put the SCIT's dissolution on hold.
ស្នងការបានសម្រេច ផ្អាកការរំលាយ SCIT ។
Your team won't face disciplinary action either.
ក្រុមរបស់អ្នកក៏នឹងមិនប្រឈមមុខនឹង ការពិន័យផងដែរ។
Wait a minute.
រង់ចាំបន្តិច។
He was so set on dissolving the SCIT. What changed his mind?
គាត់​បាន​កំណត់​យ៉ាង​ខ្លាំង​លើ​ការ​រំលាយ SCIT ។ តើ​អ្វី​បាន​ផ្លាស់​ប្តូ​រ​ចិត្ត​របស់​គាត់?
- Didn't Yoon Dong-ju tell you? - Tell me what?
- Yoon Dong-ju មិនបានប្រាប់អ្នកទេ? - ប្រាប់ខ្ញុំពីអ្វី?
It seems that
វាហាក់ដូចជានោះ។
he met with Min Ju-yeong and settled things.
គាត់បានជួបជាមួយ Min Ju-yeong និងដោះស្រាយរឿង។
Settle what?
ដោះស្រាយអ្វី?
This is interesting.
នេះគួរឱ្យចាប់អារម្មណ៍។
So you're willing to take as many hits as you've given
ដូច្នេះ អ្នក​សុខ​ចិត្ត​ទទួល​បាន ​ការ​ទស្សនា​ច្រើន​ដូច​ដែល​អ្នក​បាន​ផ្តល់​ឲ្យ
as long as I leave the SCIT alone?
ដរាបណាខ្ញុំចាកចេញពី SCIT តែម្នាក់ឯង?
That's right.
នោះជាសិទ្ធិ។
Just get rid of me.
គ្រាន់តែកម្ចាត់ខ្ញុំ។
A man shouldn't be so petty and drag other people into things.
បុរស​មិន​គួរ​តូច​ចិត្ត​ខ្លាំង​ពេក ហើយ​អូស​ទាញ​អ្នក​ដទៃ​ចូល​ក្នុង​រឿង។
Our problem should be resolved between us.
បញ្ហារបស់យើងគួរតែត្រូវបានដោះស្រាយរវាងយើង។
You're here to apologize, yet you seem so brazen.
អ្នកមកទីនេះដើម្បីសុំទោស ប៉ុន្តែអ្នកហាក់ដូចជាព្រហើនណាស់។
All right.
មិនអីទេ។
We're friends. A friend can do that much.
យើងជាមិត្ត។ មិត្តម្នាក់អាចធ្វើបានច្រើន។
But we're in different weight classes,
ប៉ុន្តែយើងស្ថិតក្នុងថ្នាក់ទម្ងន់ខុសៗគ្នា
so we should balance the scales.
ដូច្នេះយើងគួរតែថ្លឹងថ្លែង។
If you're still standing after getting beaten up
ប្រសិនបើអ្នកនៅតែឈរ បន្ទាប់ពីវាយ
I'll think about what to do.
ខ្ញុំនឹងគិតអំពីអ្វីដែលត្រូវធ្វើ។
Who does he think he is, Jesus?
តើ​លោក​យេស៊ូ​ស្មាន​ថា​លោក​ជា​នរណា?
Why take on all the burden?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាទទួលយកបន្ទុកទាំងអស់?
Are you always like this?
តើអ្នកតែងតែបែបនេះទេ?
I guess I somewhat knew, but you're beyond help.
ខ្ញុំគិតថាខ្ញុំដឹងខ្លះហើយ ប៉ុន្តែអ្នកលើសពីជំនួយ។
Just go.
គ្រាន់តែទៅ។
I was an idiot to think you were decent.
ខ្ញុំជាមនុស្សល្ងង់ដែលគិតថាអ្នកសមរម្យ។
He hasn't come to the on-call room in days.
គាត់មិនបានមក បន្ទប់ហៅទូរស័ព្ទប៉ុន្មានថ្ងៃមកហើយ។
Where in the world is he?
តើគាត់នៅឯណានៅលើពិភពលោក?
Where's the gym Dong-ju used to go to?
តើកន្លែងហាត់ប្រាណ Dong-ju ធ្លាប់ទៅនៅឯណា?
It's called Victory Gym in Dongho-dong.
វាត្រូវបានគេហៅថា Victory Gym នៅ Dongho-dong។
- Thank you. - But…
- សូមអរគុណ។ - ប៉ុន្តែ…
It's Victory Gym in Dongho-dong!
វាជាកន្លែងហាត់ប្រាណ Victory Gym នៅ Dongho-dong!
VICTORY GYM
កន្លែងហាត់ប្រាណ VICTORY
Excuse me, is Yoon Dong-ju here?
សូមទោស Yoon Dong-ju នៅទីនេះ?
I don't know.
ខ្ញុំមិនដឹងទេ។
STEAMED BUN
នំដុត
DUNG-JU
ឌុង-ជូ
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE ME, BUT ANSWER YOUR PHONE
ខ្ញុំដឹងថាអ្នកមិនចង់ឃើញខ្ញុំទេ ប៉ុន្តែឆ្លើយទូរស័ព្ទរបស់អ្នក
IF YOU DON'T, YOU'RE DEAD
បើអ្នកមិនធ្វើទេ អ្នកស្លាប់ហើយ។
TEXT FROM STEAMED BUN MISSED CALL FROM STEAMED BUN
អត្ថបទពីនំចំហុយ ខកខានការហៅពីនំចំហុយ
VICTORY GYM
កន្លែងហាត់ប្រាណ VICTORY
Have you experienced any discomfort lately?
តើ​អ្នក​ធ្លាប់​ជួប​ប្រទះ​នឹង ​ភាព​មិន​ស្រួល​ក្នុង​ពេល​ថ្មី​ៗ​នេះ​ទេ?
Anything like hand tremors or blurry vision?
មាន​អ្វី​ខ្លះ​ដូច​ជា​ញ័រ​ដៃ ឬ​មើល​មិន​ច្បាស់?
Maybe sudden moments of dizziness?
ប្រហែលជាវិលមុខភ្លាមៗ?
Why do you ask?
ហេតុអ្វីបានជាអ្នកសួរ?
The repeated impacts sustained during your athletic career
ផលប៉ះពាល់ម្តងហើយម្តងទៀតដែលមាននិរន្តរភាព ក្នុងអំឡុងពេលអាជីពកីឡារបស់អ្នក។
may have caused brain damage.
អាចបណ្តាលឱ្យខូចខួរក្បាល។
They call it becoming punch-drunk.
ពួកគេហៅវាថាស្រវឹង។
You might be okay right now,
អ្នកប្រហែលជាមិនអីទេឥឡូវនេះ
but the symptoms can get worse.
ប៉ុន្តែរោគសញ្ញាអាចកាន់តែអាក្រក់ទៅ ៗ ។
I recommend an in-depth examination.
أنصح بمراجعة متعمقة.
Just getting home?
هل وصلت للتو إلى المنزل؟
- I don't see him around at all. - Excuse me?
- لا أراه موجودًا. - عذرًا؟
The guy who followed you around like a mutt.
الرجل الذي يتبعك هو مثل الملاحق.
Did you two fight?
هل تشاجرتم؟
What's wrong with him?
ما خطبه؟
They say he has a cold.
يقولون أنه مصاب بنزلة برد.
He got a shot this afternoon, but he's still listless.
تم إطلاق النار عليه بعد ظهر اليوم ، لكنه لا يزال غير مدرج في القائمة.
My goodness, why is this mutt making me worry so much?
يا إلهي، لماذا تجعلني حزينًا جدًا؟
He won't eat either.
وهو لن يأكل أيضًا.
- Can I? - Yeah.
- هل يمكنني؟ - نعم.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Dung-ju, have some sausage.
دونج جو لديه بعض النقانق.
Goodness, he's eating it.
حسنًا، إنه يأكله.
He's eating.
إنه يأكل.
Are you eating it because the sweet lady gave it to you?
هل تأكله لأن امرأة أعطتك إياه؟
Goodness.
الخير.
Do you feel better now?
هل تشعر بحال جيدة الآن؟
STEAMED BUN
خبز مخبوز
DUNG-JU
دونغ جو
WHERE ARE YOU? DID YOU EAT? ARE YOU SICK?
أين أنت؟ هل أكلت؟ هل أنت مريض؟
I'M GOING TO STOP TALKING TO YOU
سأتوقف عن الحديث معك.
CONTACT ME OR YOU'LL REALLY REGRET IT
اتصل بي أو سوف تندم.
Still can't get in touch with Dong-ju?
هل لا تزال غير قادر على الاتصال بـ دونغ جو؟
No.
لا
The little punk is driving me absolutely crazy.
الحشرة الصغيرة تقودني إلى الجنون.
DUNG-JU
دونغ جو
What kind of champion gets beaten up?
ما نوع البطل الذي هزم؟
How humiliating.
كم هو محرج.
I couldn't think of a way to beat Min Ju-yeong,
لا أستطيع أن أفكر في طريقة للتغلب على مين جو يونغ.
no matter how hard I racked my brains.
بغض النظر عن مدى صعوبة تفكيري،
I don't have anything or any influence.
ليس لدي أي تأثير.
But then I thought it over and realized.
ولكن بعد ذلك فكرت في الأمر وأدركت.
I know how to take hits.
أعرف كيفية الحصول على المشاهدات.
I'm really good at taking hits.
أنا جيد جدًا في التأثير.
So I thought that was the only way.
لذا أعتقد أن هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة.
I could protect us.
أنا أستطيع حمايتنا.
That's why I did it. I'm sorry.
لهذا السبب فعلت ذلك. أنا آسف.
I'll leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
Hey, Yoon Dong-ju.
مرحبا يون دونغ جو.
Good job.
أحسنت.
So is that it?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Is that what you want to do?
هل هذا ما تريد فعله؟
Do you want to give up now?
هل تريد الإستسلام الآن؟
So?
لذا؟
Should we stop?
هل يجب علينا التوقف؟
No.
لا
I won't give up.
لن أستسلم أبدًا.
Why would I?
لماذا انا؟
Lying on the floor
النوم على الأرض
isn't humiliating.
ليس عيبا.
That's just how life is.
هكذا هي الحياة.
You push through it,
لقد دفعت من خلاله،
enduring it with gritted teeth.
تحملها بأسنانك المشدودة.
If you can hold on and stay down without getting turned over,
إذا كنت تستطيع أن تتحمل ذلك ولا تنظر إلى الوراء.
you can get back up and fight again.
يمكنك النهوض والقتال مرة أخرى.
It doesn't matter how many times you fall…
بغض النظر عن عدد المرات التي تسقط فيها...
As long as you get back up.
طالما أنك تتعافى.
The fight isn't over.
المعركة لم تنتهي بعد
There are still more rounds to go.
لا زال هناك المزيد من الجولات.
- They say everything has its purpose. - What are you doing? Stop being gross.
يقولون إن لكل شيء غاية. ماذا تفعل؟ توقف عن السوء.
Why are you leaving that little mutt of a cop alone?
لماذا تركت هذا الشرطي بمفرده؟
- Where are the rest of the precursors? - He only heard that there was a delay
- أين أذهب أولاً؟ - لقد سمع للتو أن هناك تأخيرًا.
due to customs clearance procedures.
بسبب الإجراءات الجمركية.
This one's a bit too much.
هذا كثير جدًا.
It is, isn't it?
نعم صحيح؟
- If there are red fire ants… - This is our chance.
- إذا كان هناك نمل ناري أحمر... - هذه فرصتنا.
You can stay at my place.
يمكنك البقاء في مكاني.
Breath. Tremors. Wind.
نفس. اهتزاز. هواء.
You take everything into account.
تأخذ كل شيء في الاعتبار.
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.
There are days…
هناك يوم...
That feel like a stray bullet.
لقد شعرت وكأنها رصاصة طائشة.
Subtitle: Jenny Kim
الترجمة الفرعية: جيني كيم